hamptons.co.uk 2012-11-21

# Hamptons - Privacy Policy - Hamptons International Real Estate Agents

#### Data protection

Hamptons International acts in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998.

We respect the privacy of our visitors and do not rent, sell or deal in any personal information with third parties. On occasion your details may be shared with Hamptons International approved contractors or agents to alert you of relevant Hamptons International products and services that you have asked to be notified of. Any information you provide will be treated in confidence and used only for the purpose for which you provided it.

Hamptons International website uses robust security protocols to ensure that personal data that is collected is done so in a secure way. 

You do not need to provide any personal information to use this site.

You can at anytime remove your details from Hamptons International website database through your **My Hamptons** account. If you do not wish to receive further marketing related materials from Hamptons International branch, please email your local branch office. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file stored on your computer that retains information about pervious visits to a website.

Hamptons International website will attempt to drop a cookie on your computer when visiting our site. If you are registered, cookies allow us to automatically log you in. They can also speed up form filling by automatically filling in parts of forms with information that you have provided on a previous visit.

Hamptons International does not use cookies to collect personal information regarding the use of your PC or internet browsing in any way. 

We respect the privacy of personal email accounts and will not send you unwanted email messages or junk mail.

Your details will not be passed to any organisation outside Hamptons International without your explicit permission.

If you have given us permission, we may email you messages to keep you up to date with news about our current services, as well as anything you express an interest in, either online or through other contact with Hamptons International.

If you do not want to be kept informed by email please login into your **My Hamptons** account and amend your account details. If you no longer wish to receive further marketing related materials from Hamptons International branch, please email your local branch office. 

For more information about the type of cookies we used, please visit our page on Cookies.
